Guide to the Harriet Wasserman Literary Agency Records, 1940s-2000 and undated (bulk 1978-1995) RL.00509
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, A-Z, 1941-1995
  - Writings (Books) Subseries, A-Z, 1944-1994 and undated
    - Hijuelos, Oscar (continued) (Box WB-13)
      - The Mambo Kings Play Songs of Love, 22
        - paperback: American (2 printings, acknowledged), movie tie-in, British, Danish (2 printings), Dutch (2 printings) German, French (2 printings), Hungarian, Korean (2 volumes), Portuguese, Spanish (Box WB-13)
        - paperback: Greek (Box WB-25)
        - uncorrected bound proof (2, acknowledged); British uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-13)
      - Mr. Ives Christmas, 3
        - hardback (slip-case edition) (Box WB-13)
        - uncorrected bound proof (acknowledged) (Box WB-13)
        - paperback: Greek (Box WB-25)
    - Hijuelos, Oscar (continued) (Box WB-14)
      - Our House in the Last World, 4
        - hardback: American, German, Spanish (Box WB-14)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-14)
    - Horwitz, James
      - They Went Thataway (Box WB-14)
    - Humphreys, Josephine, 3
      - Dreams of Sleep
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-14)
      - My Real Invisible Self in A World Unsuspected
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-14)
      - Rich in Love
        - paperback: American (dedicated) (Box WB-14)
    - Hyder, O. Quentin
      - Shape Up
        - paperback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-14)
    - Ivory, James, and Ismail Merchant
      - English Landscape
        - hardback: American (inscribed by Ivory) (Box WB-14)
    - Jacobson, Howard, 2
      - In the Land of Oz (Box WB-14)
      - Peeping Tom (Box WB-14)
    - Jhabvala, Ruth Prawer, 29
      - Amrita (or To Whom She Will), 3
        - paperback: American, German (2 printings) (Box WB-14)
      - A Backward Glance
        - paperback: French (Box WB-14)
      - Esmond in India
        - paperback: American (Box WB-14)
      - Heat and Dust, 7
        - hardback: German, Finnish (Box WB-14)
        - paperback: American, Romanian, Spanish, Italian, Slovenian (Box WB-14)
      - The Householder, 2
        - paperback: American, British (Box WB-14)
      - In Search of Love and Beauty, 4
        - hardback: American (inscribed), Swedish (Box WB-14)
        - paperback: (British) (Box WB-14)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-14)
      - The Man With the Dog in Love in Full Bloom
        - paperback: American (Box WB-14)
      - The Nature of Passion
        - paperback: Spanish (Box WB-14)
      - Poet and Dancer, 4
        - hardback: American, British (Box WB-14)
        - paperback: French (Box WB-14)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-14)
      - A New Dominion, 2
        - paperback: British, English (published in India) (Box WB-14)
    - Jhabvala, Ruth Prawer (continued) (Box WB-15)
      - Three Continents, 4
        - paperback: American, Italian, Spanish (Box WB-15)
        - uncorrected, bound proof (Box WB-15)
      - Travelers
        - paperback: American (Box WB-15)
    - Jonnes, Jill
      - We're Still Here: the Rise, Fall, and Resurrection of the South Bronx
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-15)
    - Kennan, George, 14
      - Around the Cragged Hill: A Personal and Political Philosophy
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-15)
      - The Decline of Bismarck's European Order: Franco-Russian Relations, 1875-1890
        - hardback: American (Box WB-15)
      - Empire of the Czar: A Journey Through Eternal Russia (Box WB-15)
      - The Fateful Alliance
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-15)
      - The Marquis de Custine and His Russia in 1839
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-15)
      - Memoirs: 1925-1950, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-15)
        - paperback: German (Box WB-15)
      - The Nuclear Delusion, 3
        - hardback: Japanese (Box WB-15)
        - paperback: Flemish, French (Box WB-15)
      - Russia, the Atom, and the West
        - paperback: German (Box WB-15)
      - Sketches From a Life, 2
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-15)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-15)
      - The State Department Policy Planning Staff Papers 1947-1949 (foreword by Kennan) (Box WB-15)
    - King, Francis, 9
      - The Action
        - hardback: British (Box WB-15)
      - Act of Darkness (Box WB-15)
      - Flights
        - hardback: British (Box WB-15)
    - King, Francis (continued) (Box WB-16)
      - One is a Wanderer (Box WB-16)
      - Punishments
        - hardback: British (Box WB-16)
      - Visiting Cards
        - uncorrected bound proof: British (Box WB-16)
      - Voices in an Empty Room, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-16)
        - uncorrected bound proof: British (Box WB-16)
      - The Woman Who Was God (Box WB-16)
    - Klein, Elizabeth, 3
      - Reconciliations
        - hardback: American (Box WB-16)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-16)
    - Klein, Kenneth
      - Getting Better: A Medical Student's Story
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
    - Koperwas, Sam, 3
      - Hot Stuff
        - hardback: American (Box WB-16)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-16)
      - Westchester Bull
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-16)
    - Kotker, Norman, 3
      - The Earthly Jerusalem
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
      - Miss Rhode Island
        - hardback: American (Box WB-16)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
    - Krahn, Fernando, 19
      - Abe Lincoln's Beard (illustrated by Krahn) (Box WB-16)
      - Alvilda Og Petronius
        - hardback: Danish (Box WB-16)
      - Arthur's Adventure in the Abandoned House (Box WB-16)
      - Dorotea Och Maximilian
        - hardback: Danish (Box WB-16)
      - The First Peko-Neko Bird, 2
        - hardback: American, German (Box WB-16)
      - A Funny Friend From Heaven (Box WB-16)
      - The Great Ape: Being the True Version of the Famous Saga of Adventure and Friendship Newly Discovered
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
      - A Flying Saucer Full of Spaghetti
        - hardback: Danish (Box WB-16)
      - Hildegarde and Maximilian
        - hardback: Danish (Box WB-16)
      - How Santa Clause Had a Long and Difficult Journey Delivering His Presents, 2
        - hardback: Japanese (Box WB-16)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
      - Little Love Story (Box WB-16)
      - Mr. Top (Box WB-16)
      - The Possible Worlds of Fernando Krahn, 2
        - hardback: American, British (Box WB-16)
      - The Self-Made Snowman (Box WB-16)
      - Sleep Tight, Alex Pumpernickel (Box WB-16)
      - Strella's Children (Box WB-16)
    - Kreyling, Michael, 3
      - Author and Agent: Eudora Welty and Diarmuid Russell, 3
        - hardback: American (Box WB-16)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-16)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-16)
    - Kuskin, Karla (6) (Box WB-17)
      - Alexander Soames: His Poems (Box WB-17)
      - The Bear Who Saw the Spring (Box WB-17)
      - Herbert Hated Being Small (Box WB-17)
      - Jerusalem, Shining Still (Box WB-17)
      - Square as a House (Box WB-17)
      - The Walk the Mouse Girls Took (Box WB-17)
    - Lansbury, Coral (12)
      - Felicity (Box WB-17)
      - The Grotto, 8
        - hardback: American, British, French (2 editions), German (Box WB-17)
        - paperback: American, French (Box WB-17)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-17)
      - Ringarra (Box WB-17)
      - Sweet Alice, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-17)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-17)
    - Lasson, Robert, 2
      - Glue It Yourself: Woodworking Without Nails (Box WB-17)
      - If I Had a Hammer: Woodworking With Seven Basic Tools (Box WB-17)
    - Lawrence, Seymour
      - Seymour Lawrence: Publisher
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-17)
    - Lee, Laurel, 14
      - Barnaby Frost (Box WB-17)
      - Barnaby Frost Plants a Seed (Box WB-17)
      - Godspeed: Hitchhiking Home, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-17)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-17)
      - Mourning into Dancing, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-17)
        - uncorrected advance proof (Box WB-17)
      - Signs of Spring, 2
        - paperback: Portuguese (Brazil) (Box WB-17)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-17)
      - Walking Through the Fire, 6
        - hardback: American (inscribed), German, Japanese (Box WB-17)
        - paperback: American, Portuguese (Box WB-17)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-17)
    - Leviant, Curt (Box WB-18)
      - The Yosemite Girl (Box WB-18)
    - Levin, Phyllis, 2
      - Abigail Adams, hardback: American paperback: American (Box WB-18)
    - Lindbergh, Anne, 9
      - Bailey's Window (Box WB-18)
      - The Hunky-Dory Dairy, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-18)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-18)
      - Next Time, Take Care (Box WB-18)
      - Osprey Island (Box WB-18)
      - The Prisoner of Pineapple Place
        - paperback: American (Box WB-18)
      - Three Lives to Live (Box WB-18)
      - Tidy Lady (Box WB-18)
      - Travel Far, Pay No Fare (Box WB-18)
    - Lowndes, Natalya, 2
      - Angel in the Sun
        - hardback: British (Box WB-18)
      - Chekago (Box WB-18)
    - Malamud, Bernard, 3
      - Pictures of Fidelman: An Exhibition
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-18)
      - Rembrandt's Hat
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-18)
      - The Tenants
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-18)
    - Markus, Julia, 9
      - American Rose, 2
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-18)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-18)
      - A Change of Luck, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-18)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-18)
      - Dared and Done: The Marriage of Elizabeth Barrett and Robert Browning, 2
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-18)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-18)
      - Friends Along the Way, 2
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-18)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-18)
      - A Patron of the Arts in Two Novellas by Julia Markus and Barbara Reid
        - paperback: American (Box WB-18)
    - Marschall, Richard, 2
      - That Old Gang O' Mine
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-18)
      - Introduction to The Tough Coughs as He Ploughs the Dough (by Dr. Seuss)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-18)
    - McCully, Emily, 4 (Box WB-19)
      - Annie Flies the Birthday Bike (illustrator) (Box WB-19)
      - Amzat and His Brothers (illustrator) (Box WB-19)
      - The Butterfly Birthday (illustrator) (Box WB-19)
      - In My Tent (illustrator) (Box WB-19)
    - McDermott, Alice, 23
      - At Weddings and Wakes, 6
        - hardback: American (acknowledgment), British, German (Box WB-19)
        - paperback: British, Dutch (Box WB-19)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-19)
      - A Bigamist's Daughter, 2
        - hardback: Japanese (Box WB-19)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-19)
      - That Night, 15
        - hardback: American, British, German, Italian, Japanese, Swedish (Box WB-19)
        - paperback: American (2 printings), British, Dutch, French, German, Portuguese (Portugal, 2 editions), Spanish (Box WB-19)
    - McDonough, Tom, 3
      - Light Years, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-19)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-19)
      - Virgin With Child
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-19)
    - McMahon, Thomas, 8
      - Loving Little Egypt, 3
        - hardback: American (Box WB-19)
        - paperback: British, Dutch (Box WB-19)
      - On Size and Life, 4
        - hardback: American (inscribed), Spanish, Flemish (Box WB-19)
        - paperback: Italian (Box WB-19)
        - hardback: Japanese (Box WB-25)
      - Principles of American Nuclear Chemistry: A Novel (Box WB-19)
    - McPhee, Charles
      - Stop Sleeping Through Your Dreams
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-19)
    - Meir, Menahem (Box WB-20)
      - My Mother, Golda Meir: A Son's Evocation of Life with Golda Meir (Box WB-20)
    - Melamed, Frances
      - Janova
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-20)
    - Merchant, Ismail, 2
      - Passionate Meals
        - hardback: American (Box WB-20)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-20)
      - The Films of Merchant Ivory (by Robert Emmet Long) (Box WB-20)
    - Milbauer, Barbara
      - The Law Giveth: Legal Aspects of the Abortion Controversy
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-20)
    - Mooney, Ted, 12
      - Easy Travel to Other Planets, 8
        - hardback: British (Box WB-20)
        - paperback: American (trade and mass market), Dutch, French, German, Swedish (Box WB-20)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-20)
      - Traffic and Laughter, 4
        - hardback: American, Italian (Box WB-20)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-20)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-20)
    - Mrosovsky, Kitty
      - Hydra
        - hardback: British (Box WB-20)
    - Myers, Walter Dean, 26
      - The Black Pearl and The Ghost (Box WB-20)
      - Brainstorm, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-20)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-20)
      - Crystal (Box WB-20)
      - Fast Sam, Cool Clyde, and Stuff, 2
        - hardback: American, Finnish (Box WB-20)
      - Fly, Jimmy, Fly!
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-20)
      - The Golden Serpent (Box WB-20)
      - Harlem Blues
        - paperback: French (Box WB-20)
      - It Ain't All For Nothing, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-20)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-20)
      - The Legend of Tarik (Box WB-20)
      - Me, Mop, and the Moondance Kid (Box WB-20)
      - Mojo and the Russians, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-20)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-20)
    - Myers, Walter Dean (continued) (Box WB-21)
      - Motown and Didi: A Love Story (Box WB-21)
      - Mr. Monkey and the Gotcha Bird (Box WB-21)
      - The Outside Shot (Box WB-21)
      - Scorpions, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-21)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-21)
      - Social Welfare (Box WB-21)
      - Sweet Illusions
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - Victory for Jamie
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - Won't Know Till I Get There
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-21)
      - The World of Work: A Guide to Choosing a Career (Box WB-21)
      - The Young Landlords (Box WB-21)
    - Naumoff, Lawrence
      - Rootie Kazootie (Box WB-21)
    - Neil, Barbara, 2
      - Someone Wonderful
        - hardback: American (Box WB-21)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
    - Nunez, Sigrid
      - A Feather on the Breath of God
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-21)
    - O'Dell, Scott, 3
      - Island of the Blue Dolphins
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - My Name is Not Angelica, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-21)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-21)
    - Parker, Peter, 2
      - Ackerley: A Life of J.R. Ackerley, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-21)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-21)
    - Panter, Carol
      - Beany and His New Recorder
        - hardback: American (dedicated) (Box WB-21)
    - Peters, Natasha, 18
      - Blues in the Night
        - paperback: British (Box WB-21)
      - Dangerous Obsession
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - Darkness Into Light, 3
        - hardback: Dutch (Box WB-21)
        - paperback: Norwegian, Swedish (Box WB-21)
      - The Enticers, 5
        - hardback: Dutch (Box WB-21)
        - paperback: American, German, Norwegian, Swedish (Box WB-21)
      - The Immortals, 2
        - paperback: Norwegian, Swedish (Box WB-21)
      - Savage Surrender
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - Splendid Torment
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - Star Dust
        - paperback: American (Box WB-21)
      - Wild Nights (3)
        - paperback: British, Norwegian (Box WB-21)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-21)
    - Pogrebin, Letty Cottin (Box WB-22)
      - Stories for Free Children
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
    - Previn, Dory
      - Bog Trotter: An Autobiography with Lyrics (Box WB-22)
    - Price, Reynolds, 11
      - The Annual Heron
        - paperback: American signed and numbered copy (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - Christ Child's Song at the End of Night
        - paperback: American limited edition inscribed (Box WB-22)
      - Country Mouse, City Mouse, 1
        - paperback: American limited edition inscribed (Box WB-22)
      - An Early Christmas
        - hardback: American signed and numbered copy (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - The Foreseeable Future, 2
        - hardback: American (dedicated) (Box WB-22)
        - uncorrected bound proof (dedicated) (Box WB-22)
      - The Good News According to Mark
        - paperback: American numbered edition (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - The Honest Account of a Memorable Life: An Apocryphal Gospell
        - hardback: American signed and numbered copy (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - Lessons Learned: Seven Poems
        - paperback: American lettered edition (signed) (Box WB-22)
      - Nine Mysteries (Four Joyful, Four Sorrowful, One Glorious)
        - hardback: American limited edition (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - Noon Rest, Best Day
        - paperback: American limited printing (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - Oracles
        - hardback: American numbered and signed edition (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - Presence and Absence
        - hardback: American limited edition (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
      - Real Copies
        - paperback: American signed and lettered edition (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
    - Rachlin, Nahid, 2
      - Foreigner
        - paperback: American (Box WB-22)
      - Married to a Stranger (Box WB-22)
    - Raskin, Ellen, 5
      - A and The, or William T.C. Baumgarten Comes to Town (Box WB-22)
      - And It Rained (Box WB-22)
      - A Child's Christmas in Wales (by Dylan Thomas, woodcuts by Raskin)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-22)
      - Figgs and Phantoms
        - paperback: American (Box WB-22)
      - The Mysterious Disappearance of Leon (I mean Noel)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-22)
    - Saint Phalle, Therese de
      - The Clearing
        - paperback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-22)
    - Seidler, Tor, 12
      - The Dulcimer Boy, 2
        - hardback: American (drawings by David Hockney), Flemish (Box WB-22)
      - A Rat's Tale, 4
        - hardback: British, Dutch, Japanese (Box WB-22)
        - paperback: British (Box WB-22)
      - The Tar Pit, 6
        - hardback: American, Dutch, Flemish (Box WB-22)
        - paperback: American, Italian, Swedish (Box WB-22)
    - Seldes, Lee, 2
      - The Legacy of Mark Rothko, 2
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-22)
        - paperback: British (acknowledged, with corrections sheet) (Box WB-22)
    - Seuling, Barbara, 7
      - How to Write a Children's Book and Get it Published
        - paperback: American (Box WB-22)
      - Just Me (Box WB-22)
      - The Last Legal Spitball and Other Little-Known Facts about Sports (Box WB-22)
      - The Loudest Screen Kiss and Other Little-Known Facts About the Movies (Box WB-22)
      - The Last Cow on the White House Lawn and Other Little-Known Facts About the Presidency
        - hardback: American (dedicated) (Box WB-22)
      - You Can't Count a Billion Dollars and Other Little-Known Facts About Money (Box WB-22)
      - You Can't Eat Peanuts in Church and Other Little-Known Laws (Box WB-22)
    - Sheraton, Mimi, 3
      - Is Salami and Eggs Better Than Sex? Memoirs of a Happy Eater (Box WB-22)
      - Visions of Sugarplums: A Cookbook of Cakes, Cookies, Candies and Confections from All the Countries That Celebrate Christmas, 2
        - hardback: American revised and expanded edition (Box WB-22)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-22)
    - Simon, Norma
      - I Wish I Had My Father (Box WB-22)
    - Simonds, Nina
      - Chinese Seasons
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-22)
    - Smith, Mark, 5 (Box WB-23)
      - The Death of the Detective (Box WB-23)
      - Doctor Blues (Box WB-23)
      - Smoke Street, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-23)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-23)
      - Toyland
        - paperback: American (Box WB-23)
    - Sourian, Peter
      - At the French Embassy in Sofia: Essays and Criticism
        - paperback: American (Box WB-23)
    - Sutton, S.B., 2
      - The Day the Televisions Stopped, 2
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-23)
        - uncorrected bound proof (acknowledged) (Box WB-23)
    - Tax, Meredith, 4
      - Families (Box WB-23)
      - Passionate Women
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-23)
      - Rivington Street (2)
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-23)
        - paperback American (acknowledged) (Box WB-23)
    - Travers, P. L., 2
      - About the Sleeping Beauty (Box WB-23)
      - Mary Poppins in the Kitchen: A Cookery Book With a Story (Box WB-23)
    - Underwood, Michael, 18
      - A Clear Case of Suicide (Box WB-23)
      - A Compelling Case (Box WB-23)
      - A Dangerous Business (Box WB-23)
      - Death in Camera (Box WB-23)
      - Death at Deepwood Grange, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-23)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-23)
      - Double Jeopardy (Box WB-23)
      - Dual Enigma (Box WB-23)
      - Guilty Conscience, 3
        - hardback: American, British (large print), omnibus (Detective Book Club edition with two other authors) (Box WB-23)
      - Hand of Fate (Box WB-23)
      - The Injudicious Judge (Box WB-23)
      - A Party to Murder (Box WB-23)
      - Rosa's Dilemma (Box WB-23)
      - The Seeds of Murder (2)
        - hardback: American, British (large print) (Box WB-23)
      - The Uninvited Corpse (Box WB-23)
    - Vreuls, Diane (Box WB-24)
      - Sums: A Looking Game (Box WB-24)
    - Wahl, Jan
      - Runaway Jonah and Other Tales
        - hardback: American (dedicated and inscribed) (Box WB-24)
    - Walter, Eugene, 3
      - Delectable Dishes From Termite Hall: Rare and Unusual Recipes
        - (paperback: American) (Box WB-24)
      - The Untidy Pilgrim
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-24)
      - The Pokeweed Alphabet, Or, A Child's Garden of Vices
        - paperback: American (Box WB-24)
    - Weber, Bruce
      - Bear Pond
        - hardback: American? (inscribed) (Box WB-24)
    - Wilcox, James, 6
      - Modern Baptists, 3
        - hardback: American, British (Box WB-24)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-24)
      - North Gladiola, 3
        - hardback: British (Box WB-24)
        - paperback: British (Box WB-24)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-24)
    - Williams, Jay, 17
      - The Burglar Next Door (Box WB-24)
      - The China Expert (as Michael Delving) (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn and the Weather Machine (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn and the Swamp Monster (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn and the Anti-Gravity Paint (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn and the Universal Glue (1 or 2?)
        - uncorrected bound proof (British) (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn and the Voice From Outer Space (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn, Invisible Boy, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-24)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn, Scientific Detective (Box WB-24)
      - Danny Dunn, Time Traveler (Box WB-24)
      - The Magic Grandfather (Box WB-24)
      - A Shadow of Himself (as Michael Delving) (Box WB-24)
      - The Surprising Things Maui Did (Box WB-24)
      - The Time of the Kraken